let questions = [
    {
        question: 'Where and in what year was the first football World Cup held?',
        options: [
            'Uruguay in 1930',
            'Brazil in 1950',
            'Italy in 1934',
            'France in 1938'
        ],
        answer: 0
    },
    {
        question: 'What was the first Olympic sport to allow female players to participate?',
        options: [
            'Volleyball',
            'Basketball',
            'Football',
            'Swimming'
        ],
        answer: 1
    },
    {
        question: 'How many world titles did former Formula 1 driver Ayrton Senna win?',
        options: [
            '3 titles',
            '4 titles',
            '2 titles',
            '5 titles'
        ],
        answer: 0
    },
    {
        question: 'Who is the greatest tennis champion in the world?',
        options: [
            'Novak Djokovic',
            'Carlos Alcaraz',
            'Jannik Sinner',
            'Daniil Medvedev'
        ],
        answer: 0
    },
    {
        question: 'Which of the following sports is not part of the triathlon?',
        options: [
            'Cycling',
            'Swimming',
            'Skateboard',
            'Running '
        ],
        answer: 2
    },
    {
        question: 'In which year did Barcelona FC win its first Champions League?',
        options: [
            '1993',
            '1992',
            '1988',
            '1988'
        ],
        answer: 1
    },
    {
        question: 'How many sports are in the Paris 2024 Summer Olympics?',
        options: [
            '30',
            '32',
            '28',
            '36'
        ],
        answer: 1
    },
    {
        question: 'Where and when did cricket appear?',
        options: [
            'France in the 16th century',
            'USA, between the 18th and 19th centuries',
            'Scotland, between the 16th and 17th centuries',
            'England, between the 16th and 17th centuries'
        ],
        answer: 3
    },
    {
        question: 'Which basketball player scored 100 points against the New York Knicks?',
        options: [
            'Pete Maravich',
            'Kobe Bryant',
            'Wilt Chamberlain',
            'Michael Jordan'
        ],
        answer: 2
    },
    {
        question: 'How many times did Pele and Maradona face each other?',
        options: [
            '3',
            '0',
            '4',
            '7'
        ],
        answer: 1
    },
];